Oh, Minecrap! I cannot wait to play Minecrap. 
Do you know what my favorite thing to do is in Minecrap?
I love building bricks with Minecrap. 
Building bricks with Minecrap is the best thing
and the most amount of fun you can have while playing an app. 
I understand why all the kids are playing this game these days,
it's because they like to build brown bricks with Minecrap.
I also like to build brown bricks with Minecrap. 
It's the most fun you can possibly have.